Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Labor Movement Serials WAG.345
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Labor unions and organizations, 1890-2012; 72.1 Linear Feet in 19 record cartons, 29 manuscript boxes, 2 half manuscript boxes, and 152 flat boxes
  - Subseries I.L: Transportation Workers, 1892-2012; 17.7 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 18 manuscript boxes, and 26 flat boxes
    - United to Win: United Taxicab Workers/Communications Workers of America, Local 9411, San Francisco, CA, 1994; cuid11420 (Box 123, Folder 94)
    - Trenton Rank & File: UTF, Trenton, NJ, 1970-1972 (Box 230, Folder 8)
    - District Bulletin: UWO affiliate, circa 1970s; cuid11421 (Box 172, Folder 42)
    - Voice of Rank & File in Transportation: Voice of Rank & File in Transportation, New York, NY, 1985-1992; cuid11422 (Box 123, Folder 95, Box 198, Folder 23)
    - Grapevine: Voice of So. Cal. Teamsters for a Democratic Union- Local 572, Lynwood, CA, 1980; cuid11423 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Voice of the Rank & File in Transportation: Voice of the Rank & File in Transportation, New York, NY, circa 1980s; cuid11424 (Box 123, Folder 96, Box 232, Folder 1)
    - Warehouse Workers: Warehouse Employees Local Union, 1936; cuid11425 (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Report of President Walter P. Reuther to the 19th UAW Consititional Convention: Wayne State University, Detroit, MI, 1964 (Box 186, Folder 8)
    - Report of Proceedings of the Fourteenth Meeting of the Western Conference of Teamsters: Western Conference of Teamsters, Seattle, WA, 1950 (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Bombardier: Willow Run Bomber Local 50, Detroit, MI, 1944-1945; cuid11426 (Box 131, Folder 5-6)
    - Wisconsin Teamster: Wisconsin Teamsters, Inc./Wisconsin Teamsters Joint Council No. 39, Milwaukee, WI, 1986; cuid11427 (Box 123, Folder 97)
    - 692 Newsletter, 1980; cuid11428 (Box 123, Folder 98)
    - Hot Cargo, 1992; cuid11429 (Box 123, Folder 99)
    - Northwest Passage: Seattle, WA, 1970-1986; cuid11430 (Box 131, Folder 7-8, Box 132, Folder 1-5)
    - Railroading: Alliance, NE, 1993; cuid11431 (Box 123, Folder 101)
    - Transport Bulletin (Taxi Edition), 1937-1940; cuid11432 (Box 83, Folder 11)
- Series II: Labor Law, 1905-2007; 10.8 Linear Feet in 13 manuscript boxes, 4 record cartons, and 3 flat boxes
  This series collects various serials and publications relevant to labor law and legislation. Topics include the development and introduction of Occupational Safety and Health legislation (often through regional organizations like Chicago's CACOSH or Connecticut's ConnectiCOSH); efforts to raise the minimum wage (Ad Hoc Committee for Workers' Compensation; National Unemployed Network; UNITE); and general trade commentary on jobs and employment (Daily Labor Report; publications by the National Labor Law Center).
  - Workers' Compensation Update: Ad Hoc Committee for Workers' Compensation, New York, NY, 1985; cuid9324 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration in the Schools: American Arbitration Association, New York, NY, 1995; cuid9325 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - ALC Newsletter: American Labor Conference on International Affairs, New York, NY, 1944 (Box 233, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Action: American Labor Party, New York, NY, 1947 (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - Labor News: Amnesty International of the USA, San Francisco, CA, 1979; cuid9326 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Brief: Associated Industries of New York State, Inc., Albany, NY, 1977; cuid9327 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - What's New in Collective Bargaining Negotiations & Contracts: Bureau of National Affairs, 1976; cuid9328 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Daily Labor Report: Bureau of National Affairs, Inc., Washington, DC, 1955, 1995; cuid9329 (Box 96, Folder 1-20)
  - Personnel Policies Forum: Bureau of National Affairs, Inc., Washington, DC, 1965; cuid9330 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Retail Services Labor Report: Bureau of National Affairs, Inc., Washington, DC, 1978; cuid9331 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Service Industries Labor Report: Bureau of National Affairs, Inc., Washington, DC, 1955; cuid9332 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Union Labor Report's On The Line: A Guide for Union Stewards: Bureau of National Affairs, Inc., Washington, DC, 1983, 1988, 1989, 1993; cuid9333 (Box 172, Folder 47)
  - CACOSH: Chicago Area Committee on Occupational Safety & Health, Chicago, IL, 1975-1980; cuid9334 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Child Labor Monitor: Child Labor Coalition, Washington, DC, 1994-1997; cuid9335 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - What is ConnectiCOSH: ConnectiCOSH, CT, circa 1970s; cuid9336 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - ECOSH News: Electronics Committee on Safety and Health, Mountain View, CA, 1978-1979; cuid9337 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Grapevine: Grassroots Organizers in the Chicago-Calumet Region, New York, NY, 1982; cuid9338 (Box 162, Folder 25)
  - Safety First: Greater New York Safety Council, Brookfield, WI, 1997; cuid9339 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Hazards: Hazards Publications Ltd., Chicago, IL, 1994-1999, 2006-2007; cuid9340 (Box 162, Folder 22)
  - HRDI Advisory: Human Resources Development Institute, Washington, DC, 1980 (Box 183, Folder 7)
  - LLR: Legal-Legislative Reporter news Bulletin: International Foundation of Employee Benefit Plans, Milwaukee, WI, 1988; cuid9341 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Highlights from April 4th, 2001 National Student Labor Day of Action: Jobs with Justice, New Brunswick, NJ, cuid9342 (Box 162, Folder 16)
  - A Call to Come to a National Congress of the Unemployed: JOIN, Chicago, IL, 1983; cuid9343 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - La Verdad / The Truth: La Verdad, Berkeley, CA, 1979; cuid9344 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Overtime: Labor Commission of the New America Movement, Chicago, IL, 1982 (Box 183, Folder 15, Box 184, Folder 6)
  - Labor Organizers Defense Fund Bulletin: Labor Organizers Defense Fund, New York, NY, 1976 (Box 180, Folder 15)
  - Comparative International Industrial Relations: Labor Law Journal, Chicago, IL, 1973; cuid9345 (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - LOHOP Catalog: Labor Occupational Health Program, New York, NY, 1991; cuid9346 (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Speak Out for Safety & Health: Maryland Committee on Occupational Safety & Health (MaryCOSH), New York, NY, 1979, 1981; cuid9347 (Box 172, Folder 71)
  - Lump-Sum City Newsletter: Massachusetts Organization of Disabled Workers, Washington, DC, 1981; cuid9348 (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Occupational Health Project: Medical Committee for Human Rights, Washington, DC, 1973; cuid9349 (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - Tri-State Economic Justice Network: Metropolitan Center for Resource and Advocacy, New York, NY, 1986 (Box 205, Folder 10)
  - Annual & Anniversary Reports: National Child Labor Committee, New York, NY, 1944 (Box 203, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report: National Child Labor Committee, New York, NY, 1928-1949 (Box 203, Folder 2-5)
  - Changing Years: National Child Labor Committee, Washington, DC, 1954; cuid9350 (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - Child Employing Industries - Proceedings of the Sixth Annual Conference: National Child Labor Committee, Boston, MA, 1910 (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - Child Labor: National Child Labor Committee, New York, NY, 1905 (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - Child Labor - A Menace to Industry, Education and Good Citizenship: National Child Labor Committee, New York, NY, 1906 (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - Child Labor and Progress: National Child Labor Committee, New York, NY, 1908 (Box 203, Folder 6)
  - Child Workers of the Nation - Proceedings of the Fifth Annual Conference: National Child Labor Committee, New York, NY, 1909 (Box 202, Folder 3)
  - Uniform Child Labor Laws - Proceedings of the Seventh Annual Conference: National Child Labor Committee, New York, NY, 1911 (Box 202, Folder 5)
  - National Civic Federation Review: National Civic Federation, Washington, DC, 1906-1911; cuid9351 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Jobs Impact Bulletin: National Committee for Full Employment, Washington, DC, 1985-1988; cuid9352 (Box 95, Folder 21)
  - Report to the Nation: National Council for a Permanent FEPC, Washington, DC, 1945; cuid9353 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Studies in Personnel Policy: National Industrial Conference Board, Inc., New York, NY, 1955 (Box 181, Folder 11)
  - NIOSH Alert: National Institute for Occupational Safety and Health, Washington, DC, 1995; cuid9354 (Box 95, Folder 22)
  - National Labor Law Center Shopsheets: National Labor Law Center, Washington, DC, 1982; cuid9355 (Box 95, Folder 23)
  - Plant Closings & Runaway Industries: Strategies for Labor: National Labor Law Center/National Lawyers Guild, McKeesport, PA, 1981; cuid9356 (Box 95, Folder 24)
  - Seventh Annual Report of the National Labor Relations Board: National Labor Relations Board, Washington, DC, 1942 (Box 188, Folder 6)
  - Right to Work National Newsletter: National Right to Work Committee, 1956; cuid9357 (Box 95, Folder 25)
  - Healthy Office Report: National Safe Workplace Institute, Linden, NJ, 1991; cuid9358 (Box 95, Folder 26)
  - National Unemployed News: National Unemployed Network, New York, NY, 1983-1984; cuid9359 (Box 95, Folder 27)
  - Reconversion: New Century Publishers, New York, NY, 1945; cuid9360 (Box 95, Folder 28)
  - News: New Jersey Committee for Occupational Safety and Health (NJCOSH), New York, NY, 1980; cuid9361 (Box 95, Folder 29)
  - Newsletter: New York Committee for Occupational Safety and Health, Albany, NY, 1984; cuid9362 (Box 95, Folder 30)
  - NYCOSH Bi-Weekly: New York Committee for Occupational Safety and Health, Inc., Durham, NC, 1997-1998; cuid9363 (Box 95, Folder 31)
  - Newsletter: New York Labor-Management Council of Health and Welfare Plans, Inc., 1971; cuid9364 (Box 172, Folder 46)
  - Jobs Hot Line: New York State Department of Labor, Albany, NY, 1978 (Box 193, Folder 4)
  - Collective Bargaining Settlements in New York State: New York State Department of Labor, Division of Research and Statistics, 1981 (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - HELP-NJ Update: NJ Right to Know & Act Coalition, 1990; cuid9365 (Box 95, Folder 32)
  - NCOSH Safety & Health News: North Carolina Occupational Safety and Health Project (NCOSH), Philadelphia, PA, 1980-1984; cuid9366 (Box 95, Folder 33)
  - Copy Right: NYSUT United Teachers, Providence, RI, 1980; cuid9367 (Box 163, Folder 48)
  - OEDA Newsletter: Occupational and Environmental Diseases Association, Madison, WI, 1998-1999; cuid9368 (Box 95, Folder 34)
  - Working Together: Ontario Ministry of Labour, San Francisco, CA, 1982; cuid9369 (Box 95, Folder 35)
  - Get Organized! Seize The Time In '77 - Build A National Workers Organization: Organizing Committee for a National Workers Organization, San Francisco, CA, 1977; cuid9370 (Box 162, Folder 26)
  - Safer Times: Philadelphia Area Project on Occupational Safety and Health (PHILAPOSH), Nashville, TN, 1977-1984; cuid9371 (Box 95, Folder 36)
  - Are You Concerned About Health & Safety on the Job: Tennessee Committee on Occupational Safety and Health (TNCOSH), circa 1970s; cuid9372 (Box 95, Folder 37)
  - Minimum Wage Revisited: UNITE, Milwaukee, WI, 1995; cuid9373 (Box 163, Folder 46)
  - Labor Law and Practice in Spain: United States Department of Labor Bureau of Labor Statistics, Milwaukee, WI, 1965; cuid9374 (Box 163, Folder 43)
  - Labor Law and Practice in Turkey: United States Department of Labor, Bureau of Labor Statistics, Milwaukee, WI, 1963; cuid9375 (Box 163, Folder 42)
  - Proceedings: Workers Defense League, New York, NY, 1969; cuid9376 (Box 163, Folder 35)
  - WYNCOSH: Western New York Council on Occupational Safety and Health, circa 1970s; cuid9377 (Box 163, Folder 26)
  - Health & Safety News: Wisconsin Committee on Occupational Safety & Health, 1988 - 1989; cuid9378 (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - WISCOSH: Wisconsin Committee on Occupational Safety and Health, Sheffield, England, 1979; cuid9379 (Box 95, Folder 51)
  - Statistics on Operations: Supplement to the Annual Report: Albany, NY, 1978 (Box 188, Folder 8-9)
  - Corporate Welfare: The Other ADFC (Aid to Financially Dependent Companies) Part 2, 1995 (Box 194, Folder 4)
- Series III: Labor News, 1897-2002; 11.6 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 8 manuscript boxes, and 19 flat boxes
  This series contains a range of daily and weekly labor newspapers, journals, trade magazines, and other publications, often chronicling labor activity -- unionization, collective bargaining, plant closings -- at the regional level, for example Denver, Colorado's Rocky Mountain Workers' Voice; Miami's Union Record of Florida; and Pennsylvania's Mon Valley Update.
  - Redwood Empire Labor Journal: All American Federation of Labor Unions in Northwestern California, Eureka, CA, 1953; cuid9380 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - American Co-Operative News: American Co-Operative News, Cambridge, MA, 1897; cuid9381 (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - Conspiracy in Coal: Appalachian Movement Press, Huntington, WV, circa 1970s; cuid9382 (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - Harlan & Bell Kentucky 1931-2 - National Miner's Union: Appalachian Movement Press, Huntington, WV, 1972; cuid9383 (Box 172, Folder 48)
  - When Southern Labor Stirs: Appalachian Movement Press, Huntington, WV, 1972; cuid9384 (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - Wage Earner: Association of Catholic Trade Unionists, Detroit, MI, 1945; cuid9385 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Wildcat: Black & Red, Detroit, MI, 1974; cuid9386 (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - Black Hawk Labor News: Black Hawk Union AFL-CIO / Hawkeye Area Labor Council, AFL-CIO, Cedar Falls, IO, 1954; cuid9387 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Black Lung Bulletin: Black Lung Association, Charleston, WV, 1971; cuid9388 (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - Newsletter: Bridge & Tunnel Officers Benevolent Association, 1984; cuid9389 (Box 163, Folder 8)
  - Monthly Labor Review: Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1939; cuid9390 (Box 163, Folder 47)
  - Inside Labor Relations: Business Research Publications, Washington, DC, 1995; cuid9391 (Box 163, Folder 9)
  - Job Safety Consultant: Business Research Publications, Inc., New York, NY, 1985; cuid9392 (Box 163, Folder 10)
  - White Collar Management: Business Research Publications, Inc., New York, NY, 1979; cuid9393 (Box 163, Folder 11)
  - Union Plus: Better Living for Union Members and Their Families: Cadmus Custom Publishing, Boston, MA, 1995; cuid9394 (Box 163, Folder 12-13)
  - Working Papers in Labor Studies: Center for Labor Studies, Seattle, WA, 1997; cuid9395 (Box 163, Folder 14)
  - Central Trades News: Central Trades & Labor Council of Nassau-Suffolk Counties, Hicksville, NY, 1958; cuid9396 (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Wages and the Working Day: Charles H. Kerr & Company, Chicago, IL, 1946; cuid9397 (Box 163, Folder 15)
  - Labor World: Chattanooga Central Labor Union, Chattanooga, TN, 1946; cuid9398 (Box 164, Folder 2-6)
  - CPSR Newsletter: Computer Professionals for Social Responsibility, Palo Alto, CA, 1990 (Box 183, Folder 5)
  - War Worker: Cummings Publishing House, Los Angeles, CA, 1944 (Box 230, Folder 11)
  - UWOC News: Dayton Unemployed Workers Organizing Committee, Dayton, OH, 1972; cuid9399 (Box 163, Folder 16)
  - Wage Rates and Hours of Labour in Canada: Department of Labour, Ottawa, Ontario, Canada, 1943; cuid9400 (Box 163, Folder 17)
  - Employment Trends: Division of Employment, New York, NY, 1970; cuid9401 (Box 163, Folder 18)
  - Southern Labor: E.T. O'Connell, Atlanta, GA, 1949 (Box 185, Folder 12)
  - Employment News: Employment News, Inc., Columbus, OH, 1993; cuid9402 (Box 163, Folder 19)
  - No More Jobs: Employment Project, New York, NY, 2002; cuid9403 (Box 163, Folder 20)
  - Federated Press Central Bureau: Federated Press, Detroit, MI, 1932; cuid9404 (Box 166, Folder 4)
  - Federated Press Eastern Bureau: Federated Press, New York, NY, 1952; cuid9405 (Box 166, Folder 5-7)
  - Federated Press Special AFL Convention Service: Federated Press, 1953; cuid9406 (Box 166, Folder 8)
  - Federated Press Special CIO Convention Service: Federated Press, 1952; cuid9407 (Box 166, Folder 9)
  - Federated Press Special Labor Day Service Annual Review: Federated Press, 1953; cuid9408 (Box 166, Folder 10)
  - Federated Press Washington Bureau: Federated Press, Washington, DC, 1952; cuid9409 (Box 167, Folder 1-2)
  - Florida Labor Advocate: Florida Labor Advocate, Tampa, FL, 1954; cuid9410 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Freie Arbeiter Stimme / Free Voice of Labor: Freie Arbeiter Stimme / Free Voice Labor, New York, NY, 1971-1976 (Box 213, Folder 18)
  - Labor Herald: Herald Cooperative Press, Baltimore, MD, 1942-1976; cuid9411 (Box 149, Folder 18, Box 175, Folder 1-7)
  - Bulletin: ILA Pacific Coast District 38, San Pedro, CA, 1938 (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - Working Paper Series: Industrial Relations Center, Minneapolis, MN, 1992; cuid9412 (Box 163, Folder 21)
  - Backgrounder: Institute for Food and Development, Oakland, CA, 1996 (Box 198, Folder 2)
  - Industrial Relations: A Journal of Economy & Society: Institute of Industrial Relations, University of California, Berkeley, Berkeley, CA, 1972 (Box 186, Folder 4)
  - Inter-American Labor News: Inter-American Confederation of Workers (C.I.T.), Washington, DC, circa 1970s; cuid9413 (Box 162, Folder 24)
  - Trade Union World - Briefing: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions - ICFTU, 2002; cuid9414 (Box 163, Folder 49)
  - International Labor News Service: International Labor News Service, Washington, DC, 1946; cuid9415 (Box 163, Folder 22)
  - Wall Street by Anna Rochester: International Pamphlets - Labor Research Association, circa 1970s; cuid9416 (Box 163, Folder 23)
  - Wage-Labour and Capital: International Publishers, New York, NY, 1933; cuid9417 (Box 163, Folder 24)
  - Wages and Profits in Wartime: International Publishers, New York, NY, 1941; cuid9418 (Box 163, Folder 25)
  - Union Record of Florida: J. Barnes, Miami, FL, 1952; cuid9419 (Box 163, Folder 50)
  - Labor Pains Newsletter: Labor Pains, Cambridge, MA, 1973 (Box 200, Folder 5)
  - Labor Party Press: Labor Party Press, Washington, DC, 1997-2000 (Box 221, Folder 1)
  - Revolt in Portugal: Labor Publications, Inc, New York, NY, 1974 (Box 199, Folder 9)
  - Labor's Press of Delaware County: Labor's Press of Delaware County, Chester, PA, 1938 (Box 231, Folder 1)
  - Labor's Voice: Labor's Voice Publishing Company, Louisville, KY, 1948-1950; cuid9420 (Box 164, Folder 7, Box 213, Folder 9)
  - Lansing Labor News: Lansing Labor News, Inc., Lansing, MI, 1954; cuid9421 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Proceedings: Local 1199, 1987; cuid9422 (Box 163, Folder 27)
  - Daily World / Mundo Diario: Long View Publishing Co., Inc., New York, NY, 1977-1978 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Voz del Pueblo: Long View Publishing Co., Inc., New York, NY, 1977-1985 (Box 216, Folder 5-9, Box 217, Folder 1-2)
  - Milwaukee Labor Press: Milwaukee County Labor Council, Milwaukee, WI, 1971 (Box 210, Folder 6)
  - Minnesota Labor: Minnesota State CIO Council, Minneapolis, MN, 1954; cuid9423 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Minutes of EEC: Minutes of EEC, USA, Undated (Box 205, Folder 11)
  - Mon Valley Update: Mon Valley Unemployed Committee, Homestead, PA, 1990; cuid9424 (Box 163, Folder 28)
  - Reporter: Mon Valley Unemployed Committee, McKeesport, PA, circa 1970s; cuid9425 (Box 163, Folder 29)
  - National Organized Labor Journal: N.O.L.J. LTD., New York, NY, 2000; cuid9426 (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - New Orleans News Digest: N.O.L.J. LTD., New Orleans, La, 1942; cuid9427 (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - National Asbestos Victims' Update: National Asbestos Victims' Legal Action Organizing Committee, circa 1970s; cuid9428 (Box 163, Folder 30)
  - Uncommon Sense: National Jobs for All Coalition, New York, NY, circa 1970s; cuid9429 (Box 163, Folder 31)
  - Plant Closings Bulletin: New American Movement, Chicago, IL, 1981; cuid9430 (Box 163, Folder 32)
  - New York City Crisis: New York Coalition to Fight Inflation & Unemployment, New York, NY, circa 1970s; cuid9431 (Box 163, Folder 33)
  - Union Label News: New York Times Chapel, 1941; cuid9432 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - New York Workers' News & Perspective: New York Workers' News & Perspective, Brooklyn, NY, 1978; cuid9433 (Box 164, Folder 8)
  - East Coast Organizer: NYC Coalition for Jobs and Services/Baltimore and Philadelphia Strike Support Organizing Committees, New York, NY, 1972; cuid9434 (Box 163, Folder 34)
  - Labor Front: Organization Publishing Co, New York, NY, 1936 (Box 210, Folder 3)
  - Fox Valley Labor News: Organized Labor in the Fox Valley, Aurora, IL, 1953; cuid9435 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Pacific Weekly: Pacific Associates, Carmel, CA, circa 1970s; cuid9436 (Box 162, Folder 21)
  - Pacific Weekly: A Western Journal of Fact and Opinion: Pacific Associates, Carmel, CA, 1936 (Box 220, Folder 14)
  - Global Electronics Information Newsletter: Pacific Studies Center, Mountain View, CA, 1982-1983 (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - United Labor News: Published Monthly in the Interest of the Men and Women Who Work, Canton, OH, 1981; cuid9437 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - Rocky Mountain Workers' Voice: Rocky Mountain Workers' Voice, Denver, CO, circa 1970s; cuid9438 (Box 173, Folder 19)
  - Information Bulletin: State of California Department of Industrial Relations, San Francisco, CA, 1980 (Box 183, Folder 9)
  - State Labor News: State Publishing Company, Columbus, OH, 1957 (Box Shared Tamiment 048, Folder 14)
  - Labor-Management Relations Service Newsletter: U.S. Conference of Mayors, Washington, DC, 1980; cuid9439 (Box 163, Folder 36)
  - Unemployment Handbook: Unemployed Workers Organizing Committee, Portsmouth, NH, circa 1970s; cuid9440 (Box 163, Folder 37)
  - U.W.O.C. National News: Unemployed Workers' Organizing Committee, San Leandro, CA, 1975; cuid9441 (Box 165, Folder 1-2)
  - Unemployed Organizer: Unemployed Workers' Organizing Committee, Chicago, IL, 1977; cuid9442 (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - Union Reporter: Union Reporter Association, Pennsauken, NJ, 1973-1986; cuid9443 (Box 165, Folder 4-6, Box 166, Folder 1-2)
  - Vermilion County Star: Vermilion County Pub. Association, Danville, IL, 1953; cuid9444 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Voz del Pueblo: Voz del Pueblo, New York, NY, 1976-1981 (Box 216, Folder 1-4, Box 217, Folder 3-5)
  - Wage Slave: Wage Slave, Hancock, MI, 1909 (Box 233, Folder 3)
  - Wildcat: Wildcat Press, Chicago, IL, 1969-1970; cuid9445 (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Where We Stand - Labor's Road Forward: Workers Age Publishers, circa 1970s; cuid9446 (Box 163, Folder 38)
  - Standing Up: Workers Rights Center, Minneapolis, MN, circa 1970s; cuid9447 (Box 163, Folder 39)
  - Working Today News: Working Today, New York, NY, 1996; cuid9448 (Box 163, Folder 40)
  - Job Hunt News: Youth Services, New York, NY, 1940; cuid9449 (Box 163, Folder 41)
  - Labor News & Commentary: Nashua, NH, 1986; cuid9450 (Box 163, Folder 44)
  - League Bulletin Contents, 1977; cuid9451 (Box 163, Folder 45)
  - The Holy Terror: Passaic, NJ, 1926 (Box 198, Folder 8)
- Series IV: International Labor Organizations, 1894-2010; 18.7 Linear Feet in 5 record cartons, 15 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, and 26 flat boxes
  This series collects various uncataloged serials and publications documenting the labor movement outside of the United States. The series contains significant quantities of material documenting unionization in Canada -- organizations include the Canadian Labour Congress; Canadian Union of Public Employees; and the Co-Operative Union of Canada -- as well as in Europe. The series also contains reports and publications issued by international bodies concerning globalization, environmental regulation, and regionally specific elements of the labor movement, specifically in Vietnam (Vietnamese Trade Unions); Japan ("Problems and Difficulties" of Japanese Workers Today: Towards the Extraction of Needs); the United Kingdom (Future of British Agriculture).
  - Class Struggle and the Strike (United States): A. Reay, Manchester, England, 1971; cuid9452 (Box 123, Folder 109)
  - Travail et Travailleurs en France: Acheve d'imprimer, Paris, France, 1989-1993; cuid9453 (Box 123, Folder 110)